{
    "1": {
        "Question":"Hey, I heard that you are a huge fan of Dee.",
        "Answer":"Deez nuts!"
    },
    "2": {
        "Question":"Excuse me, but do you like pudding?",
        "Answer":"Well how about pudding deez nuts in your mouth?"
    },
    "3": {
        "Question":"You want some free CDs?",
        "Answer":"Well how about you see deez nuts!"
    },
    "4": {
        "Question":"Do you know what gagging is?",
        "Answer":"Well how about you gag on these nuts!"
    },
    "5": {
        "Question":"Do you like Megamind?",
        "Answer":"Well I hope you don't megamind me putting these nuts in your mouth!"
    },
    "6": {
        "Question":"Have you heard about my friend Wilya?",
        "Answer":"Wilya suck deez nuts?"
    },
    "7": {
        "Question":"Do you like Wendy's",
        "Answer":"When deez nuts go in your mouth?"
    },
    "8": {
        "Question":"Hey man, are you leaving?",
        "Answer":"Leaving deez nuts in your mouth!"
    },
    "9": {
        "Question":"Hey do you know Bofa?",
        "Answer":"Bofa deez nuts!"
    },
    "10": {
        "Question":"Do you like parodies?",
        "Answer":"Well how'd you like a pair o' deez nuts in ya mouth?!"
    },
    "11": {
        "Question":"For how long do you gargle?",
        "Answer":"Well how about you gargle on deez nuts!"
    },
    "12": {
        "Question":"Do you know Candice?",
        "Answer":"Well can deez nuts fit in your mouth?"
    },
    "13": {
        "Question":"So you're gonna be a goblin for halloween?",
        "Answer":"You're gonna be goblin deez nuts!"
    },
    "14": {
        "Question":"Have you met my friend Philip?",
        "Answer":"Flip on deez nuts!"
    },
    "15": {
        "Question":"Have you heard about the news in Kenya today?",
        "Answer":"Kenya fit deez nuts in ya mouth?"
    },
    "16": {
        "Question":"Do you prefer the Yankees or the Expos?",
        "Answer":"Yank on deez nuts!"
    },
    "17": {
        "Question":"Do you like Imagine Dragons?",
        "Answer":"Imagine dragging deez nuts over your head!"
    },
    "19": {
        "Question":"Do you like Vanessa Paradis?",
        "Answer":"How about a pair of deez nuts!"
    },
    "20": {
        "Question":"Have you heard of E10 the space ship?",
        "Answer":"Eatin deez nuts!"
    },
    "21": {
        "Question":"I just got Ligma?",
        "Answer":"Ligma balls!"
    },
    "22": {
        "Question":"Yo, I just got diagnosed with SDN?",
        "Answer":"How about a pair of deez nuts!"
    },
    "23": {
        "Question":"Did you hear what happened in Norway?",
        "Answer":"Norway deez nuts can fit in your mouth!"
    },
    "24": {
        "Question":"Do you know my friend Hans?",
        "Answer":"Hands on deez nuts!"
    }
}

